

Jesse Briata

Cyber Security Analyst

7028260877 · jbriata23@protonmail.com

Skills
Cyber Security
Fast Learner
Content Writing
Computer Networking
Penetration Testing
Python
Linux Administration
Blue Team
Research
Ability to Work in a Team
Linux Hardening
Marketing Strategy

Profile

Technical Writer Specializing In Cyber-Security And Crypto-Currency

Expert Technical Writer with outstanding knowledge of editing, writing marketing, and content creation on Cyber-Security, Crypto-Currency, and Fin-Tech. Knowledge of modern writing and editing styles. Successful at updating and maintaining technical records. Motivated to learn, grow and excel in the world of Cyber and Crypto

Employment History

Digital Marketing Manager / Content Creator, King Dice Academy, Las Vegas

September 2021 - November 2021

Build King Dice Academy Wordpress from scratch. Write press release, biography, memebership types, and articles on Craps tournaments. Maintain membership subscriptions. Customer support. Manage King Dice Reddit, Twitter, Facebook, and YouTube. Contact Casino management and generate leads for King Dice Academy

Lead Technical Writer, John McAfee, Remote

June 2021 — September 2021

Determine the clearest and most logical way to present complex information about the legacy of John Mcafee, cryptocurrency in general, the specifics of the tokenomics of whackd, and cyber-security related subject matter, as if the reader had no knowledge on the subject.

Generate innovative ideas for medium articles, memes, digital marketing strategies, etc.

Meet with subject-matter experts to ensure specialized topics are appropriately addressed.

Analyze information required for the development or update of policy, procedure and form documentation.

Review and/or copyedit content developed by other members of the team

Senior Content Writer, StrongNode.io, Remote

May 2021 — August 2021

Lead on the day-to-day management of the StrongNode Telegram, Reddit,

Twitter, and all digital platforms, while creating inspirational, informative and engaging content

Create over 200 unique works of content a day

Effectively translate the innovations of Edge computing as an innovative take on Decentralized cloud computing to a complete beginner in IT

Develop creative ideas, suggest new innovative ways of delivering digital content and keep up-to-date with the latest digital marketing trends.

Create graphics and edit photos, working with the internal design team when necessary.

Create awareness and interest within our audiences and stakeholder groups, driving traffic to engage with digital content.

Prioritize and schedule work effectively, anticipating problems and adjusting the allocation of resources and time accordingly.

Contribute to and work with relevant team and stakeholders to develop, manage and implement the digital side of integrated marketing campaign

Technical Writer, Third Gen Media, Remote

February 2020 - May 2021

Writes about all manner of subject matter such as paralegal analysis, home renovation, fashion etc all on a contract basis with 12 hour turn around time 2000-3000 words

Adheres to and updates in-house style guide.

Updates, edits, and proofreads written materials such as product manuals, user manuals, how-to guides, and FAQs.

Works closely with subject matter experts, engineers, developers, and product marketing team.

Monitors analytics on usage of online product training materials as well as those embedded within the product.

Collects user data to determine areas of documentation that need revision and updating.

May serve on quality design, product development, or user experience teams.

Director of Operations/ AV Technician, Holo, New York City

June 2019 — December 2019

Set up and operate sound and video equipment used to conduct live events for DJs, bands, sound artists, and large-scale festivals

Mix soundboards, use visual controllers, enhance lighting, and coordinate graphics.

Received tech rider from incoming artists, and set up the event accordingly. Manage DI boxes, cables, mixing gear, fog machine equipment, etc and keep it organized in a neat and accessible manner.

Work with constantly evolving, complex problems to find quick solutions.

General Manager, Rhinoceropolis, Denver

June 2011 — September 2019

Maintain daily operations including setting up complex sound systems, booking regional and international acts, organizing accommodations for artists, running door and bar, paying artists, maintaining equipment and spaces.

Deejay in between artists and perform as headliner over five times a week

Managed booking, set-up and accommodation for acts such Lil Peep, Deerhunter, Yves Tumor and other lead music industry talent

Education

School of the Art Institute of Chicago, Chicago, IL

Majored in Art and Technology

CompTIA A+

CompTIA Security+

CCNA